Finding Aid for the Buffalo Musicians' Association Records, 1889-2009
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Local 533 Records, 1923-1969, II.; 3 boxes, 1 book
  - General Meeting Minutes, 1963-1968, II.A; 60 folders
    - December 10, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2806)
    - February 11, 1968, 2 leaves (Box 25, Item 2807)
    - March 3, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2808)
    - March 10, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2809)
    - April 21, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2810)
    - May 19, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2811)
    - June 9, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2812)
    - September 8, 1968, 2 leaves (Box 25, Item 2813)
    - October 13, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2814)
    - November 10, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2815)
    - December 1, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2816)
    - December 22, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2817)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, 1962-1969, II.B; 109 folders
    - December 15, 1962, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2818)
    - January 7, 1963, 2 leaves (Box 25, Item 2819)
    - February 4, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2820)
    - March 4, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2821)
    - April 1, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2822)
    - Special Board Meeting, April 27, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2823)
    - May 6, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2824)
    - June 1, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2825)
    - July 7, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2826)
    - July 27, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2827)
    - September 7, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2828)
    - October 12, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2829)
    - November 2, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2830)
    - December 21, 1963, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2831)
    - January 4, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2832)
    - January 19, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2833)
    - February 8, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2834)
    - February 22, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2835)
    - March 14, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2836)
    - April 4, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2837)
    - April 18, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2838)
    - May 9, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2839)
    - June 6, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2840)
    - July 18, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2841)
    - August 8, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2842)
    - August 22, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2843)
    - September 5, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2844)
    - Special Board Meeting, September 12, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2845)
    - September 26, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2846)
    - October 10, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2847)
    - October 31, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 25, Item 2848)
    - November 28, 1964, 2 leaves (Box 25, Item 2849)
    - December 12, 1964, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2850)
    - January 9, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2851)
    - January 30, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2852)
    - February 13, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2853)
    - February 20, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2854)
    - March 13, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2855)
    - March 20, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2856)
    - April 10, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2857)
    - May 8, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2858)
    - May 22, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2859)
    - July 10, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2860)
    - September 1, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2861)
    - September 11, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2862)
    - September 12, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2863)
    - October 2, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2864)
    - October 23, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2865)
    - November 13, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2866)
    - December 11, 1965, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2867)
    - January 2, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2868)
    - Joint Meeting of Boards of Directors: Locals 43 & 533, January 8, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2869)
    - January 8, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2870)
    - February 5, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2871)
    - March 5, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2872)
    - March 19, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2873)
    - Joint Meeting of the Executive Boards of Locals 533 and 43, March 26, 1966, 5 leaves (Box 25, Item 2874)
    - April 2, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2875)
    - April 6, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2876)
    - April 16, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2877)
    - May 7, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2878)
    - June 4, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2879)
    - July 16, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2880)
    - August 13, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2881)
    - September 3, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2882)
    - September 24, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2883)
    - October 15, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2884)
    - October 29, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2885)
    - November 12, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2886)
    - December 3, 1966, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2887)
    - January 7, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2888)
    - January 21, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2889)
    - February 4, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2890)
    - March 4, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2891)
    - March 25, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2892)
    - April 1, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2893)
    - April 8, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2894)
    - April 15, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2895)
    - April 29, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2896)
    - June 3, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 25, Item 2897)
    - June 11, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2898)
    - June 24, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2899)
    - July 22, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2900)
    - September 9, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2901)
    - September 30, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2902)
    - October 1, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2903)
    - October 7, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2904)
    - October 21, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2905)
    - November 11, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2906)
    - November 18, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2907)
    - December 30, 1967, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2908)
    - January 20, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2909)
    - February 3, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2910)
    - February 24, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2911)
    - March 9, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2912)
    - March 30, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2913)
    - April 20, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2914)
    - April 27, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2915)
    - May 18, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2916)
    - June 8, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2917)
    - July 27, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2918)
    - August 17, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2919)
    - August 31, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2920)
    - September 28, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2921)
    - October 12, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2922)
    - October 26, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2923)
    - November 9, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2924)
    - November 23, 1968, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2925)
    - January 18, 1969, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2926)
  - Correspondence, 1919-1949, II.C; 11 folders
    - July 28, 1919, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2927)
    - October 17, 1927-November 16, 1927, 3 leaves (Box 26, Item 2928)
    - January 21, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 26, Item 2929)
    - March 20, 1929, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2930)
    - March 29, 1929, 2 leaves (Box 26, Item 2931)
    - February 20, 1930, 2 leaves (Box 26, Item 2932)
    - September 8, 1933, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2933)
    - October 1, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2934)
    - October 26, 1934, 1 leaf (Box 26, Item 2935)
    - February 5, 1942, 3 leaves (Box 26, Item 2936)
    - Report of the President's Office, November 1949, 3 leaves (Box 26, Item 2937)
  - News Clippings, 1967-1986, II.D; 1 folder
    - News Clippings, 1967-1986, 4 items (Box 26, Item 2938)
  - Directory and Wage Scale Books, 1923-1965, II.E; 31 folders
    - 1923, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2939)
    - 1927, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2940)
    - 1928, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2941)
    - 1929, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2942)
    - 1930, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2943)
    - 1931, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2944)
    - 1932, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2945)
    - 1934, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2946)
    - 1935, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2947)
    - 1936, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2948)
    - 1937, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2949)
    - 1938, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2950)
    - 1940, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2951)
    - 1941, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2952)
    - 1942, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2953)
    - 1943, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2954)
    - 1945, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2955)
    - 1946, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2956)
    - 1947, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2957)
    - 1948, 1 booklet (Box 27, Item 2958)
    - 1949, 1 booklet (Box 28, Item 2959)
    - 1950, 1 booklet (Box 28, Item 2960)
    - 1951, 1 booklet (Box 28, Item 2961)
    - 1952, 1 booklet (Box 28, Item 2962)
    - 1953, 1 booklet (Box 28, Item 2963)
    - 1954, 1 booklet (Box 28, Item 2964)
    - 1956, 1 booklet (Box 28, Item 2965)
    - 1959, 1 booklet (Box 28, Item 2966)
    - 1960, 1 booklet (Box 28, Item 2967)
    - 1962, 1 booklet (Box 28, Item 2968)
    - 1965, 2 booklets (Box 28, Item 2969)
  - Attendance Records, 1931-1968, II.F; 1 bound volume
    - 1931-1969, 1 bound volume (Box None, Item 2970)
- Local 92 Records, 1969-2009, III.; 8 boxes
  - Meeting Minutes, 1969-1993, III.A; 4 boxes
    Grouped chronologically by month.
    - January 1969, 14 leaves (Box 29, Item 2971)
    - February 1969, 7 leaves (Box 29, Item 2972)
    - March 1969, 8 leaves (Box 29, Item 2973)
    - April 1969, 10 leaves (Box 29, Item 2974)
    - May 1969, 8 leaves (Box 29, Item 2975)
    - June 1969, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 2976)
    - July 1969, 8 leaves (Box 29, Item 2977)
    - August 1969, 8 leaves (Box 29, Item 2978)
    - September 1969, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 2979)
    - October 1969, 6 leaves (Box 29, Item 2980)
    - November 1969, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 2981)
    - December 1969, 6 leaves (Box 29, Item 2982)
    - January 1970, 7 leaves (Box 29, Item 2983)
    - February 1970, 6 leaves (Box 29, Item 2984)
    - March 1970, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 2985)
    - April 1970, 7 leaves (Box 29, Item 2986)
    - May 1970, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 2987)
    - June 1970, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 2988)
    - July 1970, 6 leaves (Box 29, Item 2989)
    - August 1970, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 2990)
    - September 1970, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 2991)
    - October 1970, 6 leaves (Box 29, Item 2992a)
    - November 1970, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 2992b)
    - December 1970, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 2993)
    - January 1971, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 2994)
    - February 1971, 7 leaves (Box 29, Item 2995)
    - March 1971, 9 leaves (Box 29, Item 2996)
    - April 1971, 10 leaves (Box 29, Item 2997)
    - May 1971, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 2998)
    - June 1971, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 2999)
    - July 1971, 8 leaves (Box 29, Item 3000)
    - August 1971, 6 leaves (Box 29, Item 3001)
    - September 1971, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3002)
    - October 1971, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 3003)
    - November 1971, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 3004)
    - December 1971, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3005)
    - January 1972, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 3006)
    - February 1972, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 3007)
    - March 1972, 10 leaves (Box 29, Item 3008)
    - April 1972, 6 leaves (Box 29, Item 3009)
    - May 1972, 6 leaves (Box 29, Item 3010)
    - June 1972, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3011)
    - July 1972, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3012)
    - August 1972, 12 leaves (Box 29, Item 3013)
    - September 1972, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3014)
    - October 1972, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3015)
    - November 1972, 9 leaves (Box 29, Item 3016)
    - December 1972, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 3017)
    - January 1973, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3018)
    - February 1973, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3019)
    - March 1973, 8 leaves (Box 29, Item 3020)
    - April 1973, 6 leaves (Box 29, Item 3021)
    - May 1973, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3022)
    - June 1973, 2 leaves (Box 29, Item 3023)
    - July 1973, 9 leaves (Box 29, Item 3024)
    - August 1973, 9 leaves (Box 29, Item 3025)
    - September 1973, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3026)
    - October 1973, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 3027)
    - November 1973, 5 leaves (Box 29, Item 3028)
    - December 1973, 4 leaves (Box 29, Item 3029)
    - January 1974, 17 leaves (Box 29, Item 3030)
    - February 1974, 13 leaves (Box 29, Item 3031)
    - March 1974, 19 leaves (Box 29, Item 3032)
    - April 1974, 13 leaves (Box 29, Item 3033)
    - May 1974, 28 leaves (Box 29, Item 3034)
    - June 1974, 10 leaves (Box 29, Item 3035)
    - July 1974, 12 leaves (Box 30, Item 3036)
    - August 1974, 22 leaves (Box 30, Item 3037)
    - September 1974, 10 leaves (Box 30, Item 3038)
    - October 1974, 11 leaves (Box 30, Item 3039)
    - November 1974, 5 leaves (Box 30, Item 3040)
    - December 1974, 6 leaves (Box 30, Item 3041)
    - January 1975, 15 leaves (Box 30, Item 3042)
    - February 1975, 11 leaves (Box 30, Item 3043)
    - March 1975, 20 leaves (Box 30, Item 3044)
    - April 1975, 22 leaves (Box 30, Item 3045)
    - May 1975, 16 leaves (Box 30, Item 3046)
    - June 1975, 3 leaves (Box 30, Item 3047)
    - July 1975, 11 leaves (Box 30, Item 3048)
    - August 1975, 9 leaves (Box 30, Item 3049)
    - September 1975, 1 leaf (Box 30, Item 3050)
    - October 1975, 6 leaves (Box 30, Item 3051)
    - November 1975, 13 leaves (Box 30, Item 3052)
    - December 1975, 10 leaves (Box 30, Item 3053)
    - January 1976, 22 leaves (Box 30, Item 3054)
    - February 1976, 13 leaves (Box 30, Item 3055)
    - March 1976, 18 leaves (Box 30, Item 3056)
    - April 1976, 17 leaves (Box 30, Item 3057)
    - May 1976, 23 leaves (Box 30, Item 3058)
    - June 1976, 2 leaves (Box 30, Item 3059)
    - August 1976, 11 leaves (Box 30, Item 3060)
    - September 1976, 14 leaves (Box 30, Item 3061)
    - October 1976, 9 leaves (Box 30, Item 3062)
    - November 1976, 11 leaves (Box 30, Item 3063)
    - December 1976, 12 leaves (Box 30, Item 3064)
    - January 1977, 6 leaves (Box 30, Item 3065)
    - February 1977, 2 leaves (Box 30, Item 3066)
    - March 1977, 14 leaves (Box 30, Item 3067)
    - April 1977, 23 leaves (Box 30, Item 3068)
    - May 1977, 18 leaves (Box 30, Item 3069)
    - June 1977, 18 leaves (Box 30, Item 3070)
    - July 1977, 22 leaves (Box 30, Item 3071)
    - August 1977, 16 leaves (Box 30, Item 3072)
    - September 1977, 19 leaves (Box 30, Item 3073)
    - October 1977, 20 leaves (Box 30, Item 3074)
    - November 1977, 12 leaves (Box 30, Item 3075)
    - December 1977, 16 leaves (Box 30, Item 3076)
    - January 1978, 17 leaves (Box 30, Item 3077)
    - February 1978, 21 leaves (Box 30, Item 3078)
    - March 1978, 21 leaves (Box 30, Item 3079)
    - April 1978, 16 leaves (Box 31, Item 3080)
    - May 1978, 19 leaves (Box 31, Item 3081)
    - June 1978, 18 leaves (Box 31, Item 3082)
    - July 1978, 14 leaves (Box 31, Item 3083)
    - August 1978, 22 leaves (Box 31, Item 3084)
    - September 1978, 13 leaves (Box 31, Item 3085)
    - October 1978, 24 leaves (Box 31, Item 3086)
    - November 1978, 12 leaves (Box 31, Item 3087)
    - December 1978, 10 leaves (Box 31, Item 3088)
    - January 1979, 10 leaves (Box 31, Item 3089)
    - February 1979, 8 leaves (Box 31, Item 3090)
    - March 1979, 10 leaves (Box 31, Item 3091)
    - April 1979, 11 leaves (Box 31, Item 3092)
    - May 1979, 9 leaves (Box 31, Item 3093)
    - June 1979, 10 leaves (Box 31, Item 3094)
    - July 1979, 10 leaves (Box 31, Item 3095)
    - August 1979, 9 leaves (Box 31, Item 3096)
    - September 1979, 10 leaves (Box 31, Item 3097)
    - October 1979, 18 leaves (Box 31, Item 3098)
    - November 1979, 11 leaves (Box 31, Item 3099)
    - December 1979, 4 leaves (Box 31, Item 3100)
    - January 1980, 13 leaves (Box 31, Item 3101)
    - February 1980, 8 leaves (Box 31, Item 3102)
    - March 1980, 14 leaves (Box 31, Item 3103)
    - April 1980, 11 leaves (Box 31, Item 3104)
    - May 1980, 12 leaves (Box 31, Item 3105)
    - June 1980, 11 leaves (Box 31, Item 3106)
    - July 1980, 5 leaves (Box 31, Item 3107)
    - August 1980, 11 leaves (Box 31, Item 3108)
    - September 1980, 13 leaves (Box 31, Item 3109)
    - October 1980, 22 leaves (Box 31, Item 3110)
    - November 1980, 6 leaves (Box 31, Item 3111)
    - December 1980, 12 leaves (Box 31, Item 3112)
    - January 1981, 12 leaves (Box 31, Item 3113)
    - February 1981, 9 leaves (Box 31, Item 3114)
    - March 1981, 16 leaves (Box 31, Item 3115)
    - April 1981, 12 leaves (Box 31, Item 3116)
    - May 1981, 10 leaves (Box 31, Item 3117)
    - June 1981, 10 leaves (Box 31, Item 3118)
    - July 1981, 8 leaves (Box 31, Item 3119)
    - August 1981, 8 leaves (Box 31, Item 3120)
    - September 1981, 8 leaves (Box 31, Item 3121)
    - October 1981, 7 leaves (Box 31, Item 3122)
    - November 1981, 8 leaves (Box 31, Item 3123)
    - December 1981, 5 leaves (Box 31, Item 3124)
    - January 1982, 6 leaves (Box 31, Item 3125)
    - February 1982, 4 leaves (Box 31, Item 3126)
    - March 1982, 5 leaves (Box 31, Item 3127)
    - April 1982, 6 leaves (Box 31, Item 3128)
    - May 1982, 6 leaves (Box 31, Item 3129)
    - June 1982, 6 leaves (Box 31, Item 3130)
    - July 1982, 7 leaves (Box 31, Item 3131)
    - August 1982, 8 leaves (Box 32, Item 3132)
    - September 1982, 6 leaves (Box 32, Item 3133)
    - October 1982, 6 leaves (Box 32, Item 3134)
    - November 1982, 6 leaves (Box 32, Item 3135)
    - December 1982, 4 leaves (Box 32, Item 3136)
    - January 1983, 5 leaves (Box 32, Item 3137)
    - February 1983, 5 leaves (Box 32, Item 3138)
    - March 1983, 8 leaves (Box 32, Item 3139)
    - April 1983, 7 leaves (Box 32, Item 3140)
    - May 1983, 5 leaves (Box 32, Item 3141)
    - June 1983, 4 leaves (Box 32, Item 3142)
    - July 1983, 5 leaves (Box 32, Item 3143)
    - August 1983, 6 leaves (Box 32, Item 3144)
    - September 1983, 5 leaves (Box 32, Item 3145)
    - October 1983, 3 leaves (Box 32, Item 3146)
    - November 1983, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3147)
    - December 1983, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3148)
    - January 1984, 4 leaves (Box 32, Item 3149)
    - February 1984, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3150)
    - March 1984, 3 leaves (Box 32, Item 3151)
    - April 1984, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3152)
    - May 1984, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3153)
    - August 1984, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3154)
    - December 1984, 3 leaves (Box 32, Item 3155)
    - March 1985, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3156)
    - May 1985, 3 leaves (Box 32, Item 3157)
    - June 1985, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3158)
    - August 1985, 4 leaves (Box 32, Item 3159)
    - September 1985, 5 leaves (Box 32, Item 3160)
    - October 1985, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3161)
    - November 1985, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3162)
    - January 1986, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3163)
    - April 1986, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3164)
    - May 1986, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3165)
    - June 1986, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3166)
    - July 1986, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3167)
    - August 1986, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3168)
    - September 1986, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3169)
    - October 1986, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3170)
    - April 1987, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3171)
    - May 1987, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3172)
    - January 1992, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3173)
    - February 1992, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3174)
    - March 1992, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3175)
    - April 1992, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3176)
    - June 1992, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3177)
    - August 1992, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3178)
    - October 1992, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3179)
    - November 1992, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3180)
    - December 1992, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3181)
    - January 1993, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3182)
    - February 1993, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3183)
    - March 1993, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3184)
    - April 1993, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3185)
    - May 1993, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3186)
    - June 1993, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3187)
    - July 1993, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3188)
    - October 1993, 2 leaves (Box 32, Item 3189)
    - November 1993, 1 leaf (Box 32, Item 3190)
  - Correspondence, 1968-1973, III.B; 1 box
    Arranged chronologically by year. Exchanges are clustered together, filed under the first dated item. If an item refers to a date in the body of the letter, or if an item is dated only by month, these are filed at the beginning of that month. Items without any date are filed in the end and labeled "undated."
    - 1970, 3 leaves (Box 33, Item 3191)
    - 1971, 36 leaves (Box 33, Item 3192)
    - January-February 1972, 20 leaves (Box 33, Item 3193)
    - March-April 1972, 25 leaves (Box 33, Item 3194)
    - May-June 1972, 36 leaves (Box 33, Item 3195)
    - July-August 1972, 50 leaves (Box 33, Item 3196)
    - September-October 1972, 59 leaves (Box 33, Item 3197)
    - November-December 1972, 40 leaves (Box 33, Item 3198)
    - 1972: undated, 11 leaves (Box 33, Item 3199)
    - January-June 1973, 43 leaves (Box 33, Item 3200)
    - July-December and undated 1973, 29 leaves (Box 33, Item 3201)
  - Receipts, 1968-1974, III.C; 1 box
    Arranged alphabetically by name of business.
    - A, 1968-1973, 82 leaves (Box 34, Item 3202)
    - B, 1968-1973, 40 leaves (Box 34, Item 3203)
    - C, 1969-1973, 7 leaves (Box 34, Item 3204)
    - D, 1968-1971, 3 leaves (Box 34, Item 3205)
    - F, 1968-1973, 30 leaves (Box 34, Item 3206)
    - G, 1969-1973, 50 leaves (Box 34, Item 3207)
    - H, 1968-1973, 9 leaves (Box 34, Item 3208)
    - I, 1969-1973, 16 leaves (Box 34, Item 3209)
    - L, 1968-1973, 25 leaves (Box 34, Item 3210)
    - M, 1968-1974, 24 leaves (Box 34, Item 3211)
    - N, 1968-1973, 103 leaves (Box 34, Item 3212)
    - P, 1970-1973, 3 leaves (Box 34, Item 3213)
    - R, 1969-1970, 8 leaves (Box 34, Item 3214)
    - S, 1968-1973, 43 leaves (Box 34, Item 3215)
    - U, 1968-1973, 29 leaves (Box 34, Item 3216)
    - V, 1969-1971, 2 leaves (Box 34, Item 3217)
    - W, 1969, 5 leaves (Box 34, Item 3218)
  - Directory and Wage Scale Books, 1969-1970, III.D; 2 booklets
    - 1969, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3219)
    - 1970, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3220)
  - Directory and Instrumentation Books, 1971-1991, III.E; 10 booklets
    - 1971, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3221)
    - 1972, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3222)
    - 1973, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3223)
    - 1974, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3224)
    - 1976, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3225)
    - 1977, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3226)
    - 1978, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3227)
    - 1979, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3228)
    - 1980, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3229)
    - 1991, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3230)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1969-1989, III.F; 2 booklets
    - 1969, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3231)
    - 1989, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3232)
  - Price Lists, 1976-1981, III.G; 3 booklets
    - 1976, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3233)
    - 1980, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3234)
    - 1981, 1 booklet (Box 35, Item 3235)
  - Directory, Instrumentation, Constitution, By-Laws, and Price List, 1995-1998, III.H; 2 books
    - 1995, 1 book (Box 35, Item 3236)
    - 1998, 1 book (Box 35, Item 3237)
- Local 649 Records, 1994-1998, IV.; 1 box
  - Financial Records, August 16, 1994, 6 leaves (Box 36, Item 3238)
  - Meeting Minutes and Financial Records, November 15, 1994, 12 leaves (Box 36, Item 3239)
  - Meeting Minutes and Financial Records, January 16, 1995, 7 leaves (Box 36, Item 3240)
  - General Membership Meeting, April 3, 1995, 3 leaves (Box 36, Item 3241)
  - Meeting Minutes, Financial Records, and Merger Request from Local 92, April 24, 1995, 11 leaves (Box 36, Item 3242)
  - Bulletin, Meeting Minutes, and Financial Records, August 7, 1995, 11 leaves (Box 36, Item 3243)
  - Bulletin, Meeting Minutes and Financial Records, August 26, 1995, 5 leaves (Box 36, Item 3244)
  - Bulletin, Meeting Minutes, and Financial Records, November 15, 1995, 10 leaves (Box 36, Item 3245)
  - Bulletin, Meeting Minutes, Financial Records, and Correspondence, January 31, 1996, 12 leaves (Box 36, Item 3246)
  - Bulletin, Meeting Minutes, and Financial Records, April 17, 1996, 9 leaves (Box 36, Item 3247)
  - Bulletin and General Membership Meeting, June 12, 1996, 2 leaves (Box 36, Item 3248)
  - Bulletin, Meeting Minutes, and Financial Records, November 13, 1996, 6 leaves (Box 36, Item 3249)
  - Bulletin, Meeting Minutes, and Financial Records, January 22, 1997, 6 leaves (Box 36, Item 3250)
  - Bulletin, Meeting Minutes, and Financial Records, April 9, 1997, 5 leaves (Box 36, Item 3251)